# **HARSH JOSHI**

# MERN STACK DEVELOPER

East Delhi 110092, Indai +91-8882103359 harshjoshi2k@gmail.com

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

Intermediate **MERN Developer** and self-motivated programmer, experience in designing and developing user interfaces using **React JS / NEXT JS** and REST API's using **Node / Express** .Skilled at utilizing a wide variety of tools and programs to provide effective applications.

#### SKILLS

React JS	Next JS	Node JS	Express JS	Tailwind CSS
Javascript	Redux Toolkit	Mongodb	Python	MUI

### **EDUCATION**

High School 2017 – 2019

Bal Bhavan Public School, Delhi

Graduated High School with 82% in 12th standard with many sports tournament certificate.

# Bachelor's / BBA[CAM], Computer Science

2019 - 2022

IIMT, GGSIPU, Delhi

Completed bachelor's with degree of Business administration and computer science with 8.4 CGPA

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## **MERN Developer**

August, 2022 - Present

#### **SNVA Ventures, Noida**

- Worked on 7 Projects which includes dashboard/CRM and web apps using React JS, Next JS, Node JS, Express JS and Mongodb.
- Key responsibilities is to write reusable and clean code with managing the flow of the web apps and CRM.

# **Data Manager and Web Dev Intern**

July, 2020 - August, 2022

#### COSP Technologies, Noida

- Helped to clean raw data from the internet using MS Excel and format according to need.
- wrote a web scrapping script using Python and develop frontend using React JS.